Denenberg, Tia Schneider Arbitration Files 6275
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Tia Schneider Denenberg Arbitration Files
1984-2004
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Denenberg, Tia Schneider
6275
65 cubic feet
40 linear ft.
Arbitration files.
6367319
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, July 15, 2013
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, August 25, 2015
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6275 AV: Tia Schneider Denenberg Arbitration Audio-Visual Materials
Children with disabilities -- Education -- United States; Unfair labor practices -- United States -- Cases; Arbitration, Industrial -- United States -- Cases; Arbitration, Industrial -- Government employees -- New York (State) -- Cases; Arbitration, Industrial -- Airlines -- United States -- Cases; Arbitration, Industrial -- Communication and traffic -- United States -- Cases; Arbitration, Industrial -- Hospitality industry -- United States -- Cases; Arbitration, Industrial -- Teachers -- Pennsylvania -- Cases; Arbitration, Industrial -- Teachers -- New York (State) -- Cases; Arbitration, Industrial -- Teachers -- Connecticut -- Cases; Arbitration, Industrial -- Teachers -- New York (State) -- Cases; Arbitration, Industrial -- Telephone companies -- New Jersey -- Cases; Arbitration, Industrial -- Electric industries -- Pennsylvania -- Cases; Arbitration, Industrial -- Electric industries -- New York (State) -- Cases; Arbitration, Industrial -- Paper industry -- United States -- Cases; Arbitration, Industrial -- Public health -- New York (State) -- Cases; Arbitration, Industrial -- Public health -- New England -- Cases; Cafiero, William F.; Campbell, Geneva; Denenberg, Tia Schneider; Frankel, Paula; Seibert, Benjamin; Williams, Joseph G.; Actors' Equity Association; AFSCME; AFSCME. Local 1501; AFSCME. Local 2507 (New York, N.Y.); AFSCME. Local 1037 (Albany, N.Y.); AFSCME. Local 3145 (Hartford, Conn.); AFSCME. Local 788 (Plattsburgh, N.Y.); AFSCME. Local 3662 (Hudson, N.Y.); Agway, Inc.; Air Line Pilots Association; Air Wisconsin; Airborne Law Enforcement Association; Alexandria Manor; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union; Amalgamated Clothing and Textile Workers Union. Local 1822 (Oswego, N.Y.); Amalgamated Transit Union. Local 1336; Amalgamated Transit Union. Local 281 (Hartford, Conn.); American Airlines; American Association of University Professors; American Federation of Government Employees. Local 491; American Federation of Government Employees. Local 2831; American Federation of Grain Millers; American Museum of Natural History; Ampthill Rayon Workers; Ansonia Copper and Brass, Inc.; Ardsley Congress of Teachers; Ardsley Union Free School District; ARI, Inc.; Arlington Central School District; Arlington Central School District (Poughkeepsie, N.Y.); Association of Flight Attendants (U.S.); Association of Poland Teachers (Poland, N.Y.); Association of Professional Flight Attendants; American Telephone and Telegraph Company; Atlantic Southeast Airways; Bakery and Confectionery Workers' International Union of America. Local 50 (New York, N.Y.); Bakery, Confectionary, Tobacco Workers, and Grain Millers International Union. Local 50 (Horsham, Pa.); Bell Atlantic Corporation; Bentley Gardens Health Care Center; Berlex Labs; Berlin Central School District; Berlin Central School District (Berlin, N.Y.); Bethlehem Central School District; BIC Corp; Big V Supermarkets, Inc.; Borden, Inc.; Bridge and Tunnel Officers Benevolent Association; Brooklyn Hospital; Brunswick Golf Course; Callahan Industries; Carthage Central School District (Carthage, N.Y.); Carthage Teachers Association (Carthage, N.Y.); Center for Optimum Care at New Haven; Champion International Corporation; Chatham Central School District (Chatham, N.Y.); Circuit-Wise, Inc.; Civil Service Technical Guild; Coastline Terminals of Connecticut, Inc.; Coca-Cola Bottling Company United (U.S.); Columbia- Green Community College; Connecticut Education Association; Corwood Laboratories, Inc.; Council of School Supervisors and Administrators; Cuno International; Dean Foods; Doane Pet Care; Duanesburg Central School District; Duanesburg Central School Teachers Association; E.I. du Pont de Nemours & Company; Englehard; Federation of University Employees. Local 34 (New Haven, Conn.); Federation of University Employees. Local 35 (New Haven, Conn.); Freeport Teachers Association; Freeport Union Free School District; Freihofer Baking Company; Globe Newspaper Co.; Goulds Pumps, Inc.; Greater Bridgeport Transit District (Conn.); Greater Bridgeport Transit District (Conn.); Greenwood Healthcare Center; Handy & Harmon; Hartford Board of Education (Hartford, Conn.); Hartford Federation of Teachers (Hartford, Conn.); Health Care Alliance, Inc.; Heinz; HNS Management Co.; Independent Oil Workers' Union; International Association of Fire Fighters. Local 760 (Hartford, Conn.); International Association of Machinists and Aerospace Workers; International Association of Machinists. Local 1379 (Elmira, N.Y.); International Brotherhood of Electrical Workers; International Brotherhood of Teamsters; International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Local 1035; International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Local 858 (Hempstead, N.Y.); International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Local 445 (New York, N.Y.); International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Local 237 (New York, N.Y.); International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Local 804 (New York, N.Y.); International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Local 182A (Syracuse, N.Y.); International Brotherhood of Teamsters. Local 559 (Enfield, Conn.); International Longshoremen's Association. Local 1398 (Hartford, Conn.); International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine & Furniture Workers. Local 475; International Union of Electronic, Electrical, Salaried, Machine & Furniture Workers. Local 247 (Brunswick, Maine); International Union of Operating Engineers. Local 106 (Clifton Park, N.Y.); Kennedy Valve Manufacturing; Kennedy Valve Manufacturing; Laidlaw Transit Services; League of Off-Broadway Theatres and Producers; Lenders Bagel Bakery; LFE Corporation; Local 8N, Graphic Communications, Inc.; Logistec Connecticut; Lone Star Industries; Long Island Rail Road.; Lucent Technologies (Firm); Marlborough Board of Education; McQuay International; Mirant New York; Mobil Oil Corporation; Mount Sinai Hospital (Cleveland, Ohio); MRC Bearings; Nassau Regional Off-Track Betting Corp. (Hempstead, N.Y.); Natchaug Federation of Registered Nurses; Natchaug Hospital; National Association of Broadcast Employees and Technicians; National Federation of Federal Employees. Local 346 (Washington, DC); National Marine Engineers' Beneficial Association (U.S.); National Maritime Union of America; National Organization of Industrial Trade Unions. Amalgamated Local 1; Nestle Food Company; New Britain (Conn). Board of Education; New Britain (Conn.). Federation of Teachers; New Britain Board of Education (New Britain, N.Y.); New Britain Federation of Teachers (New Britain, N.Y.); New England Health Care Employees Union. Paraprofessional Health Care Employees (NP-6) Bargaining Unit; New Jersey Bell; New York (City). Dept. of Education. Community School District #10; New York (City). Dept. of Education. Community School District #27; New York (City). Dept. of Education; New York (N.Y.). Board of Education; New York (N.Y.). Office of Labor Relations; New York (N.Y.). Dept. of Environmental Protection; New York (State). Dept. of Health; New York (State). Division of Youth; New York (State). State Liquor Authority; New York (State). Office of Mental Health; New York (State). Dept. of Parole; New York (State). State Insurance Fund; New York (State). Division of Housing and Community Renewal; New York (State). Banking Dept; New York (State). Dept. of Correctional Services; New York (State). Dept. of Taxation and Finance; New York (State). Dept. of Mental Hygiene; New York (State). Dept. of Transportation; New York (State). Banking Dept; New York City Health and Hospitals Corporation; New York City Housing Authority; New York State Nurses Association; New York State Nurses Association; New York State Public Employees Federation, AFL-CIO; New York State Public Employees Federation, AFL-CIO; Niagara Mohawk Power Corporation; Niskayuna Central School District; Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers International Union; Packaging Corporation of America; Pan American World Airways, Inc.; Paper, Allied-Industrial, Chemical and Energy Workers International Union; Paper, Allied-Industrial, Chemical and Energy Workers International Union. Local 254 (Pulaski, N.Y.); Peekskill City School District; Pennsylvania Power Company; Pepsi-Cola Company; Philadelphia Federation of Teachers; Pine Bush Central School District; Pine Bush Teachers Association; Poland Central School District (Poland, N.Y.); Production Service and Sales District Council. Local 300-S (Hauppauge, N.Y.); Public Service Electric and Gas Company; Ramapo Central School District #1 (N.Y.); Ramapo Central School District #2 (N.Y.); Ramapo Teachers Association; Redress (Organization); Rensselaer County Deputy Sheriff's Police Benevolent Association; Republic Airlines; Rhinebeck Central School District; Rondout Valley Central School District (Accord, N.Y.); Saint-Gobain Abrasives; Saratoga County (N.Y.). Deputy Sheriff's Benevolent Association; School District of Philadelphia, Pa; Simkings Industries; Simkins Industries; Social Service Employees Union. Local 371 (Westport, Conn.); Society of Stage Directors and Choreographers (U.S.); Sound Shore Medical Center of Westchester (New Rochelle, N.Y.); Soundview Nursing Home; Stamford Board of Education; Star Ledger; Star Ledger; State University of New York at Buffalo; State University of New York Health Science Center at Syracuse; Stella D'Oro Biscuit Company; Stillwater Central School District (Latham, N.Y.); Sweet Live Foods; TCI of Northern New Jersey; Trap Rock Corp; Triborough Bridge and Tunnel Authority; Turner & Seymour; Ulster County Sheriff's Employees Association (N.Y.); United Airlines; United Auto Workers. Local 338 (Torrington, Conn.); United Cement, Lime and Gypsum Workers International Union; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America; United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America. Local 329 (Elmira, N.Y.); United Federation of Teachers. Local 2 (New York, N.Y.); United Food and Commercial Workers International Union. Local 325 (Pittsburgh, Pa.); United Food and Commercial Workers International Union. Local 1500 (Florida, N.Y.); United Food and Commercial Workers International Union. Local 888 (Mount Vernon, N.Y.); United Food and Commercial Workers International Union. Local 371; United Paperworkers International Union; United Paperworkers International Union. Local 118 (Auburn, N.Y.); United Paperworkers International Union. Local 955 (Pulaski, N.Y.); United Paperworkers' International Union. Local 56 (Stamford, Conn.); United Public Service Employees Union (Albany, N.Y.); United States Postal Service; United States. Farmers Home Administration; United States. Dept. of Veterans Affairs; United Steelworkers of America. Local 3298 (Seneca Falls, N.Y.); United Steelworkers of America. Local 134 (Milford, Conn.); United Steelworkers of America. Local 9265; United Steelworkers of America. Local 6445 (Ansonia, Conn.); United Steelworkers of America. Local 3571 (Ansonia, Conn.); United Steelworkers of America. Local 7201 (Woodbridge, Conn.); United Transportation Union; United University Professions (Association: N.Y.); University of Connecticut; USAir (Firm); Verizon --New Jersey; Verizon Connected Solutions, Inc.; Visiting Nurse Association (New York State); Wappingers Falls (N.Y.). Police Benevolent Association; Waterford Teachers Association; Waterford-Half Moon Central School District; Watkins Glen Central School District (Watkins Glen, N.Y.); Watkins Glen Faculty Association (Watkins Glen, N.Y.); West Wynde Nursing Center; WFSB (Television station: Hartford, Conn.); Wyandanch Teachers Association (Wyandanch, N.Y.); Wyandanch Union Free School District (Wyandanch, N.Y.); Yale University
6367319
- Lone Star Industries and United Cement, Lime, Gypsum Wkrs. Local 191 Lawrence Butts AAA/PA 85-07-02-1-1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- MT Sinai Hospital and District 1199 Termination of Wilberto Pacheco AAA 84-08-04-2-1 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Mt Sinai and District 1199 Wilberto Pacheco Exhibits (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Pennsylvania Power Company & IBEW Local 272 85-03-01-2-4 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Pennsylvania Power Company and IBEW Local 272 85-12-08-1-4 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- LFE Corporation and CWU Gr. 84-53/CWA 1-85-66 AAA/HART 85-05-1-1 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Natchaug Hospital Inc. Natchaug Fed. Of Reg. Nurses, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- New York City and The Doctors' Council, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Phila. School District and Phila. Fed. Of Teachers, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Philadelphia Schl. Dist. & Phila. Fed. Tchrs., 1985 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Public Service Elec. & Gas and IBEW, Sys Council U-2, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Public Service Elec. & Gas and IBEW, council U-2, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Quinnipiac College Quinnipiac Faculty Federation, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Ramapo Teachers Association and Ramapo Central School District (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Republic Airlines and Alea Disc/Dish, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- United Airlines and IAMAW District 141, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Alexandria Manor & NEHCC Employees Union 1199, 2003 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Health Care Investors, Inc. Alexandria Manor & NE Health Care EES Union District 1199, SEIU/AFL-CIO, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- American Airlines Inc. & APFA, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Scope and Contents
  Discharge of Jared Lee
- AT&T & CWA AFL-CIO District 13 CWA, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Bentley Gardens Health care Center& NEHC Employees Union, 2002 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Chatham Central School District & Dr. Henry Clinton & Janet Byrd-Clinton, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- 1999 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Central School District & Dr. Henry Clinton & Janet Byrd-Clinton, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Chatham Central School District & Dr. Henry Clinton & Janet Byrd-Clinton, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Coca Cola and Teamsters, 125, 2000 (Box 2, Folder 10)
- NYS Dept. of Health and PEF, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- NYS Department of Health and PEF, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- NYS Dept. of Health and PEF, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Pepsi Cola and Teamsters Local 125 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- United University Professors and Dr. Charles R. Iden, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- United Airlines and IAMAW Discharge of Raynard Jones, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- united Airlines and IAMAW, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- United Airlines and IAMAW Discharge of Osama Taha, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- United Airlines and IAMAW District 141, 2000 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- United Airlines and IAMAW, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- United Airlines and IAMAW, District 141, 2001 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Greater Bridgeport Transit Union and Local 1336, ATU, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Greater Bridgeport Transit District & Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 1336 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Greater Bridgeport Transit District & Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 1336 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Greater Bridgeport Transit District & Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 1336 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Greater Bridgeport Transit District & Amalgamated Transit Union, Local 1336 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Greater Bridgeport Transit & ATU, Local 1336 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Greater Bridgeport Transit District & ATU, Local 1336 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Greater Bridgeport Transit & ATU, Local 1336 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Greater Bridgeport Transit & ATU, Local 1336 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Greater Bridgeport Transit & ATU, Local 1336 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- United Airlines & AFA Daniel Rucker - 30 Day Suspension, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- United Airlines - AFA (Box 5, Folder 2)
- United Airlines - AFA (Box 5, Folder 3)
- United Airlines & IAMAW, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- United Airlines & IAMAW (Box 5, Folder 5)
- United Airlines - IAMAW Risso (Box 5, Folder 6)
- American Airlines & APFA, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- American Airlines, Inc. & APFA, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- American Airlines, Inc. & APFA, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- NYS & PEF Highland Res Center, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- NJ Bell and IBEW Arthur Tagleiri, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- United Airlines and IAMAW, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- United Airlines and AFA, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- AFA - United Airlines (Box 6, Folder 3)
- United Airlines - AFA, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- United Airlines IAMAW, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- WFSB and NABET Brenda Kestenbaum (Box 6, Folder 6)
- WFSB-TV - NABET, AFL-CIO (Box 6, Folder 7)
- AFA - United Airlines, Grievance of Deborah Covell (Box 6, Folder 8)
- AFA - United Airlines, Inc. (Box 6, Folder 9)
- AFA - United Airlines (Box 6, Folder 10)
- AFA - United Airlines (Box 6, Folder 11)
- NABET, AFL-CIO, Claimant, and WSFB, Post-Newsweek Stations, Inc., Respondent, 1989 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  Nov 14
- wiremold & local 1040 IBEW Disc/DISCH/Judith Richman, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Yale University & Local 34, 1988 (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Yale/ Beverly Lett (Box 6, Folder 15)
- FCD Mark IV Company and CVA, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 16)
- AT&T and IBEW, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Borden, Inc. and IAMAW Local 1278, 1991 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Various Arbitration Summaries (Box 6, Folder 19)
  1. Sequoia Rock Co. - Operating Engineers Local Union No. 3; 2.C Schmidt Company - Allied Industrial Workers of America, Local 157, FMCS; 3. Anchor Supply Company - Grocery and food Warehousemen, Local 635, FMCS; 4. City of Detroit - Detroit Police Officers Association; 5. Warner Robins ALC - American Federation of Government Employees, Local 987, FMCS; 6. Eby-Brown Company - International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffers, Warehousemen and Helpers of America, Local 423; 7. Air Express International Corporation - Miscellaneous Warehousemen, Drivers and Helpers Union, Local 986; 8. AFA Testimony
- NJ Bell and IBEW, Local 827, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- NJ Bell & IBEW Disc/Lenor Ledoux, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- New Jersey Bell Telephone and IBEW Local 827, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- NYC Health & Hosp. Corp. and NYSNA, 1989 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- State of New York & PEF, John Culkin, GRVNT (Box 7, Folder 5)
- USAIR and ALPA Grievance, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- UAL & AFA - Lec Group, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 7)
- UAL/AFA - MEC - 3 & 7 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- United Airlines & AFA, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- UAL/AFA - Craig Herring (Box 7, Folder 10)
- United/AFA - Craig Herring (Box 7, Folder 11)
- United Airlines & IAMAW, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 12)
- E.I. DuPont de Nemours & Ampthill Rayon workers, 2003 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- E.I. DuPont De Nemours & Ampthill Rayon Workers (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Greenwood Healthcare Center & New England Health Care Employees union District AFL-CIO, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Lucent technologies and IBEW, System Council T-3, Local 827, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Lucent technologies, Inc. & Avaya, Inc. vs. IBEW System Council T-3 & Local 827, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Mirant New York, Inc. & Local Union No. 503 IBEW, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Department of Education of the City of New York, Community School District #27 vs. Geneva Campbell, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Community School District Ten vs. Benjamin Seibert, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Community School district Ten vs. Benjamin Street, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Community School District Ten vs. Benjamin Street, 2001 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- NYC Board of Education & United Federation of Teachers, Local 2, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- American Airlines & APFA, K. Scott, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Ardsley Schools & Teachers, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- DuPont DeNemours & United Workers, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- DuPont Denemours & United Workers, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Goodbye Safety DuPont Ampthill, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Ampthill Rayon Workers, Inc. - E. I. DuPont De Nemours and Company, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Ampthill Rayon Workers, Inc. - E. I. DuPont De Nemours and Company (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Circuit Wise and UF, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Goulds Pumps (Box 9, Folder 9)
- City of Hartford and Local 760 Health Insurance, 1995 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Local 760 - City of Hartford, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- International Association of Firefighters, Local 760 - City Hartford, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- International Association of Firefighters, Local 760 - City of Hartford, 1993 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- International Association of Firefighters, Local 760 - City of Hartford, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- International Association of Firefighters, Local 760 - City of Hartford, 1994 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Greater Bridgeport Transit & ATU, Local 1336, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- GBTD & ATU: Transcripts Vol. 1,2,3 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Greater Bridgeport Transit & ATU, Local 1336, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- GBTD & ATU: Transcript Vol 7,8,9 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Greater Bridgeport Transit & ATU, Local 1336, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Air Wisconsin & ALPA, 1992 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Agway, Inc. & Amer. Fed. Of Grain Millers, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Boston Globe & Boston Globe Employees Assn., 1989 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Boston Globe Employees Association - Boston Globe (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Boston Globe employees Association, Union, - The Globe Newspaper company, company, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Cases Cited in Employer's Post Hearing Brief (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Boston Globe Employees Association - Boston Globe, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Kennedy Valve MFG and IAMAW Local 1379 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Kraft and ACTWU FMCS, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Mansfield Bd of Ed & Mansfield Education Assn., 1991 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- City of Hartford & Local 760 IAFF, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- City of Hartford & Local 760 IAFF, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- City of Hartford & Local 760 IAFF, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- city of Hartford & Local 760 IAFF, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- UALIAMAW Breazzano, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- United Airlines and IAMAW Martinez (Box 11, Folder 6)
- United Airlines & IAMAW Echevarria (Box 11, Folder 7)
- United Airlines and IAMAW direct (Box 11, Folder 8)
- VA + AFGE FMCS AWD, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- NJ Bell 7 IBEW Local 827, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- New Jersey Bell & IBEW Local 827, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- NJ Bell and IBEW, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- NJ Bell Telephone and IBEW, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- NYC and MEBA/NMU, 1994 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Turner & Seymour and UAW, Local 1699, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- USAIR & AFA, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- USAIR & AFA, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- USAIR, Inc. - Association of Flight Attendants, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- USAIR, Inc. - Association of Flight Attendants, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- USAIR, Inc. - Association of Flight Attendants, 1992 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- United Airlines and IAMAW, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- United Airlines and IAMAW Ramon Oropeza Discharge, 1993 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- American Airlines/APFA, 1991 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- APFA - American Airlines (Box 13, Folder 2)
- APFA - American Airlines (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Farmers Home Admin and AFGE Local 2831, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Freihofer Banking Company and Local 50 BC & T, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- MRC Bearings and UAW Local 338, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Mobil oil Corp. and Indepen. Cent Oil Workers, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- New Britain Board of Ed and New Britain Fed of Tchrs, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- 1989 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- NJ Beel Tel & IBEW Local 827, 1990 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- PAN AM and ALPA, 1989 (Box 13, Folder 11)